Guide to the Edward Bradford Titchener papers,1887-1940.
Titchener, Edward Bradford papers, 1887-1940
- Correspondence
  - EBT to Dr. F. L. Dimmick, 11/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 11/10/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. F. Russell Bichowsky, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. Eva R. Goldstein, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. E. Stechert & Co., 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Frank Alien, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. P. Putnam's Sons, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. H. Pyle, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Marjorie, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Paul T. Young, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. H. B. Davis, 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. H. J. Bool (not henry, but Herbert, his son), 11/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Bureau of Standards, 11/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor Matsumoto, 11/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. T. G. Hegge, 11/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Bishop, 11/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor H. P. Weld, 11/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor A. C. Reid, 11/14/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 11/16/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 11/16/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor W. S. Foster, 11/16/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Principal E. L. Palmer, 11/16/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 11/16/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. B. H. Balckwell, 11/16/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 11/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Lyman Low, 11/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. H. J. Bool, 11/17/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. Rowland Wood, 11/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mabel F. Martin, 11/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to G. E. Stechert, 11/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor William Berry, 11/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 11/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to President W. F. Teel, 11/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. T. Carl Whitmer, 11/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to B. S. Talmey, 11/20/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 11/21/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 11/24/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 11/27/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Mr.. R. R. Smith, 11/30/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 12/4/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dr. F. L. Dimmick, 12/5/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to Dean of College of Arts and Sciences, 12/7/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to C. V. Tower, 12/13/23 (Box 4)
  - EBT to American Philosophical Society, 12/18/23 (Box 4)
  - H. Lesage to EBT, 12/21/23 (Box 4)
  - FRAGMENT EBT to Professor Fernberger, 1923 (Box 4)
  - FRAGMENT pages 2-5 of a manuscript, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Pages 1-5 of a manuscript, 1923 (Box 4)
  - 1924 (Box 5)
  - EBT to R. R. Smith, 1/8/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund C. Sanford to EBT, 1/11/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund C. Sanford to EBT, 1/13/24 (Box 5)
  - W. S. Foster to EBT, 1/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. F. L. Dimmick, 1/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 1/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. Grover C. Barnum, 1/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Dallenbach, 1/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor W. Wirth, 1/29/24 (Box 5)
  - SBT to Edmund C. Sanford, 2/1/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. L. T. Spencer, 2/2/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/5/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/6/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Ella L. Smith, 2/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to A. C. Reid, 2/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Miss Geannette R. Blumenthal, 2/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. James D. Weinland, 2/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Messrs. Brown & Delavan, 2/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. F. C. Stunner, 2/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 2/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to J. E. Van Natta, 2/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to M. A. Tinker, 2/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to G. Stanley Hall, 2/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/9/24 (Box 5)
  - G. E. Muller to EBT, 2/12/24 German (Box 5)
  - EBT to Max Meeneg, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Bishop, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. C. H. Stoelting, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor A. C. Reid, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor M. S. Washburn, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Herr E. Simmerraann, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ruckmick, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Murchison, 2/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 2/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor R. C. Givler, 2/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Foster P. Boswell, 2/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 2/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to G. A. Poynder, 2/13/2^ (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Walter S. Hunter, 2/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Wilder D. Bancroft, 2/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Otto Kleram, 2/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/14/24 (Box 5)
  - Charles Myers to EBT, 2/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Gustav Fock, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor J. R. Kantnor, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Messrs. Brown & Delavan, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Josiah Morse, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to New York Life Insurance Company, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Messrs. Treman King & Co., 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Prpfessor A. C. Gill, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Otto Kleara, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 2/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Sister Mary Basil, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to K. F. Koehlers Antiquarium, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. Mabel F. Martin, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Otto Ortmann, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor C. E. Ferree, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Winifred B. Kittredge, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. George M. Hungerford, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. W. H. French, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to. Marjorie, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to F. L. Bixley, 2/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Ogden, 2/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. Cutler, 2/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 2/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. H. Keatley Moore, 2/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. James E. Ives, 2/21/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 2/21/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to W. S. McNutt, 2/21/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E. S. Robinson, 2/21/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor A. D. Bush, 2/21/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Messrs. Brown & Delavan, 2/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 2/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. B. H. Balckwell, 2/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 2/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Ward's Natural Science Establishment, 2/23/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund Sanford to EBT, 2/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Editor of the New Rochelle Standard-Star, 2/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mssrs. Spindler and Hoyer, 2/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E. A. McC. Gamble, 2/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr. G. A. Poynder, 2/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. M. Puglisi, 2/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Isabelle S. Hackett, 2/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to the President, University of Arkansas, 2/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor R. H. Jorden, 2/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor G. L. Hamilton, 2/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 2/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas L. Elder, 2/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor D. C. Rogers, 2/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Miss Louise T. Alien, 2/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 2/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. G. A. Poynder, 2/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. F. H. Ward, 3/1/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Sturapf, 3/1/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas L. Elder, 3/1/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 3/1/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor C. W. Luh, 3/1/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Hamilton, 3/1/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 3/1/24 (Box 5)
  - Thomas Elder to EBT, 3/3/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 3/4/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/4/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 3/4/24 (Box 5)
  - Thomas Elder to EBT, 3/5/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Charles S. Myers, 3/5/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. Bostwick, 3/5/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Godfrey H. Thomson, 3/5/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to 3. H. Self, 3/5/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor H. P. Weld, 3/5/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Macmillan Company, 3/6/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to R. H. Jordan, 3/6/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. Rowland Wood, 3/6/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Col. Charles W. Furlong, 3/6/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Winifred Ifyde, 3/7/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mrs.. C. E. Ferree, 3/?/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. Thomas L. Elder, 3/7/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. F. L. Dimmick, 3/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor George Humphrey, 3/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 3/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. F. L. Dimmick, 3/8/24 (Box 5)
  - Thomas Elder to EBT, 3/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to ----, 3/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Hoisington, 3/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 3/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. Rowland Wood, 3/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Winifred Hyde, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor 3. 0. Bowman, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Weld, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The Century Company, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. Rowland Wood, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. M. J. Zigler, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor D. C. Rogers, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ruckmick, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor F. P. Bowell, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The Dean of the Graduate School, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor H. P. Weld, 3/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 3/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Herr E. Zimmermann, 3/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to K. F. Koehlers Antiquarium, 3/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Horace B. English, 3/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Frank Griffin, 3/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Eliott Frost, 3/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to J. E. Van Natta, 3/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Purchasing Department, 3/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to R. H. Jordan, 3/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to C. S. Myers, 3/15/24 (Box 5)
  - Spindler & Hoyer to EBT Encl. George Frank to EBT, 3/25/24, 3/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 3/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Godfrey Thomson, 3/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. A. Ames Jr., 3/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 3/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Foster Boswell, 3/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Messrs. R. A. Heggie, 3/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The Dean of the Graduate School, Morrill Hall, 3/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dean of the Graduate School, 3/18/24 (Box 5)
  - E. G. Boring to EBT, 3/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor W. Heinrich, 3/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 3/22/24 (Box 5)
  - E. G. Boring to EBT, 3/25/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor W. F. Willcox, 3/25/24 (Box 5)
  - E. C. Sanford to EBT, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to George S. Frank, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. C. Wilson Smith, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. R. Jaensch, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor 01 Kutzner, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Messrs. Longmans Green & Co., 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. B. H. Blackwell, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to G. Stanley Hall, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. Mario Puglisi, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Sanford, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. M. J. Zigler, 3/26/24 (Box 5)
  - Ward's Natural Science Establishment to EBT, 3/27/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Miss May Braddock, 3/27/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/27/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Charles Durham, 3/27/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Marjorie, 3/27/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor George L. Hamilton, 3/27/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. C. H. Stoetling, 3/27/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 3/27/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor W. F. Willeox, 3/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Roswell P. Angler, 3/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 3/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Winifred Hyde, 3/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to National Geographic Magazine, 3/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 3/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ruckmick, 3/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Sanford, 3/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. Frank Ward, 3/29/24 (Box 5)
  - Otto Klemm to EBT, 4/4/24 German (Box 5)
  - C. S. Myers to EBT, 4/5/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to W. S. Foster, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. J. Mck. Cattell, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Julius Pilker, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. Mario Puglisi, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor W. F. Willcox, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to World Book Company, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Miss Elizabeth Blacking, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Purchasing Department, Morrill Hall, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Winifred Hyde, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to William Yale, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. 0. H. Taylor, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor 0. L. Reiser, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor A. J. Snow, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Roswell P. Angier, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to R. R. Smith, 4/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Godfrey H. Thomson, 4/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. F. M. Urban, 4/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to W. S. Taylor, 4/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to James P. Porter, 4/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. Edmund Jacobson, 4/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The Bryant Teachers Bureau, 4/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. A. S. Mackenzie, 4/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. S. Robinson, 4/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. A. A. Roback, 4/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 4/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Messrs. Hawsley & Sons, 4/l1/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 4/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to K. F. Koehlers Antiquarium, 4/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 4/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Hoisington, 4/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Winifred Hyde, 4/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. M. J. Zigler, 4/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 4/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 4/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 4/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Seth Wakemen, 4/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Haven D. Bracket, 4/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 4/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. F. L. Wells, 4/15/24 (Box 5)
  - Charles H. Seaver to EBT, 4/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor William M. Brown, 4/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Bixley, 4/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 4/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. C. S. Myers, 4/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to D. C. Rogers, 4/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to M. W. Calkins, 4/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 4/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Scheck, 4/17/24 (Box 5)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 4/21/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to James Porter, 4/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Winifred Hyde, 4/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 4/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Charles Seaver, 4/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The Macmillan CompanyEnd. report on textbook, 4/22/24 (Box 5)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 4/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to George Alien & Unwin, 4/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Samuel W. Fernberger, 4/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Raymond Dodge, 4/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E. C. Sanford, 4/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 4/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. H. B. Davis, 4/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Haven D. Brackett, 4/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to K. F. Koehlers Antiquarium, 4/23/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund C. Sanford to EBT, 4/24/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to George M. Michaels, 4/24/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to W. H. Pyle, 4/24/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 4/24/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Ethel Bowman, 4/24/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Grace Adams, 4/24/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 4/24/24 (Box 5)
  - SBT to Professor Wilson D. Wallisy, 4/24/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Jewel Spencer, 4/24/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund C. Sanford to EBT, 4/25/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Edmund Sanford, 4/25/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. B. Boring, 4/25/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to National Geographic Magazine, 4/25/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Royal Society of Medicine, 4/25/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund Sanford to EBT, 4/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Robinson and Carpenter, 4/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to D. C. Rogers, 4/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to R. A. Heggie & Bro. Go., 4/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 4/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Michael Zigler, 4/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E.C.; Sanford, 4/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 4/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 4/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor E, C. Sanford, 4/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Br. M. F. Martin, 4/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor George Catlin, 4/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Haven D. Brackett, 4/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr. Arthur Mitchell, 4/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mario Puzlin, 5/1/24 (Box 5)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 5/2/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr. Edgar J. Banks, 5/2/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor M. F. Washburn, 5/2/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 5/2/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to M. C. Scheck, 5/2/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 5/2/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. H. P. Weld, 5/2/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor L. B. Hoisington, 5/2/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Hawsley, 5/6/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 5/6/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to W. S. Rusk, 5/6/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Wynn Jones, 5/6/34 (Box 5)
  - Rowland Wood to EBT, 5/7/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 5/7/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to S. G. Boring, 5/7/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Edwin D. Starbuck, 5/7/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Assistant Secretary, Cornell University, 5/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 5/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Winifred Hyde, 5/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 5/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. C. Waren, 5/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 5/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 5/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to DR. H. P. Weld, 5/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to A Kirschmann, 5/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Otto Klemm, 5/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Spindles & Holfer, 5/10/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund Sanford to EBT, 5/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to W. B. Pillsbury, 5/13/24 (Box 5)
  - SBT to Rowland Wood, 5/13/24 (Box 5)
  - SBT to Professor R. M. Ogden, 5/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to W. B. Pillsbury, 5/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to S Caraeron, 5/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Raymond Dodge, 5/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Hoisington, 5/l4/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor H. P. Weld, 5/l4/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 5/l4/24 (Box 5)
  - Mr. Thurber to Clark Alumni, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. Keatley Moore, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to F, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Marchison, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas L. Elder, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. P. Weld, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. A. D. Bush, 5/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 5/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. L. N. Wilson, 5/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Robinson, 5/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Miss May Braddock, 5/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor 0. L. Reiser, 5/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor T. A. Hunter, 5/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor M. F. Washburn, 5/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. M. Halverson, 5/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 5/17/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund Sanford to EBT, 5/18/24 (Box 5)
  - E3T to John Nafe, 5/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 5/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Adolfo de Hostos, 5/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Ward's Natural Science Establishment, 5/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr Edgar J. Banks, 5/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Miss Audrey Shuey, 5/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr W. M. Karston, 5/20/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr. Latham of the Macmillan Company, 5/20/24 (Box 5)
  - C. L. F. (?) to EBT, 5/21/24 (Box 5)
  - Dr. Arthur Chozecki to EBT, 5/21/24 (Box 5)
  - SBT to Mrs. C. Fadd-Franklin, 5/21/24 (Box 5)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 5/27/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr Grace Adams, 5/2?/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Sydney Alrutz, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to M. L. Reymert, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to John Grant, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Seth Wakeman, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to K. K. MacDonald, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to John Nafe, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Bishop, 5/28/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 5/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 5/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. M. J. Zigler, 5/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Miss Audrey Shuey, 5/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr William M. Marston, 5/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Jesse H. White, 5/31/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor C. A; Ruckmick, 5/31/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund C. Sanford to EBT, 6/1/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Miss Grace Adams, 6/5/24 (Box 5)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 6/6/24 (Box 5)
  - SBT to Karl Dallenbach, 6/6/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 6/7/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 6/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 6/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. Arthur Chozecki, 6/11/24 (Box 5)
  - C. A. Brewer to EBT, 6/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 6/13/24 (Box 5)
  - C. A. Brewer to EBT, 6/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The President, Clark University, 6/19/24 (Box 5)
  - Wm. Proctor McElroy to EBT, 6/22/24 (Box 5)
  - G. to EBT, 6/26/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund Sanford to EBT, 6/29/24 (Box 5)
  - May Braddock to EBT, 6/29/24 (Box 5)
  - T. A. Hunter to EBT, 6/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Garrison, 6/30/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Murchison, 7/2/24 (Box 5)
  - Edmund Sanford to EBT, 7/7/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mt. C. J. Rumsey and Co., 7/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Philip Johnson, 7/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 7/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Sydney P. Noe, 7/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to V Morosoff, 7/8/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E.G. Sanford, 7/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Wm. R. Wilson, 7/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dean of the Graduate School, Cornell University, 7/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to R. M. Ogden, 7/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to J. McK. Cattell, 7/9/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. G. H. Taylor, 7/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. Harry Belson, 7/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Bowing, 7/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to F. W. Farnberger, 7/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr. J. Baldwin, 7/10/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to the Guarantee Co, of North America, 7/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Philip Johnson, 7/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to John Watson, 7/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Morton Rymert, 7/11/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 7/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to White and Burdick, 7/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Knight Dunlop, 7/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to S. Cameron, 7/12/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Ellen, 7/12/24 (Box 5)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 7/13/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr Harry Helson, 7/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. R. Crosland, 7/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. Calvin P. Stone, 7/14/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Jesse H. White, 7/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Ballenbach, 7/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. C. Sanford, 7/15/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The President, Cornell University, 7/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to 3. W. Fernberger, 7/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to H. Keatley Moore, 7/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to F. J. E. Woodbridge, 7/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to R. M. Ogden, 7/16/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Raymond, 7/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 7/17/24 (Box 5)
  - SBT to Philip Johnson, 7/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. H. Helson, 7/17/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 7/18/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 7/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Co., 7/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to EL M. Ogden, 7/19/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Co. (enclosed manuscript), 7/21/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. von Frey, 7/21/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Hoisington, 7/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor M. F. Washburn, 7/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Thomas Elder, 7/22/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Jordan, 7/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 7/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to F. W. Johnson, 7/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. Harry Helson, 7/23/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. Arthur WoMr.ath, 7/24/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dean of The College of Arts and Sciences, 7/25/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Dr. H. G. Bishop, 7/25/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to R. R. Smith, 7/25/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Professor Donald A. Saird, 7/25/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to G. A. Poynder, 7/26/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Mr.. H. F. Daviex, 7/29/24 (Box 5)
  - EBT to Karl Dallenbach, 7/29/24 (Box 5)